houseofbrides.com 2011-06-07

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
House of Brides is committed to maintaining your confidence and administers the following Privacy Policy to protect the personally identifiable information you provide on our website. 

**What information do we collect on this website? How do we use it?**  
House of Brides collects information online to meet your requests. When you join our registry, we ask for your name, address, phone number, and e-mail address. While it is not required, we also ask for additional information about you as well as specific bridal party and wedding information. This allows us to send you information about special events and offers tailored to your needs. 

We use a third party advertising company to deliver ads on our behalf across the Internet. To help make our information more useful to our visitors, we may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website and about your interaction with our ads. We do not collect any personally identifiable information through the use of this technology. 

Credit card information submitted in online orders is processed through a secure online service for the utmost security. 

**What are cookies?**  
Cookies are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent this action. Our website uses cookies to ensure you are not shown the same content repeatedly, to deliver information that is specific to your interests, and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

**Will we disclose the information collected to outside parties?**  
The personally identifiable information we collect on our website is used so we can provide you with the best possible shopping experience. House of Brides may share your information with select retailers so you are provided with offers we believe will be of interest to our customers. If you wish to permanently opt out of these offers, please send an email to 

.

We may also use non-identifying information to improve the design of our website and to share with our advertisers. As an example, we may tell an advertiser that a given number of individuals visited a certain area on our website or that a given number of individuals who filled out our registration form are from a certain region of the U.S. We will not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

**How does House of Brides protect customer information?**  
We protect all the customer data we collect on our website. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have implemented state-of-the-art procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. 

**Is there anything else I should know?**  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information online such as through e-mail that information can be collected and used by others. In addition, the privacy policies of other websites will vary, while others may not state privacy policies. 

In short, if you provide personally identifiable information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. It is ultimately your responsibility to maintain the secrecy of your personally identifiable information to the extent you feel comfortable. We encourage you to be careful and to ask questions before you disclose your personally identifiable information to others. 

**Your consent:**  
By using our website, you consent to our collection and use of the information you provide. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If you would like to be removed from our mailing list or have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail to: 

.
